Police.
It's my partner.
We had an argument
and he has just driven off,
but he has been drinking
and he really shouldn't
be behind the wheel.
I'm worried about him.
ENGINE ROARS
TYRES SCREECH
Police.
Yes, I called earlier
and they gave me this number,
but I haven't heard anything.
Arthur Donalan.
Yes, you already said that
someone would call me back,
but no-one has!
Look, he's not
answering his phone,
and I am very worried about him.
Well...
..for God's sake, just make
sure that someone does!
CLOCK CHIMES THE HOUR
SHE GASPS
Down by a rolling river
chanced to stray
Her eyes were brown
without a frown
Martha?
In here.  Here, look what I found.
HE CHUCKLES
I must have brought them
with me from the Met.
Forgot all about them.
I should take them back to
the station, really, shouldn't I?
Or, you know, we could,
er, keep them for a while
for, erm...
..sexy time!
SHE LAUGHS
Sounds lovely.
They're rather restrictive,
I imagine.
I'm dropping off some stuff
at the charity shop first, Motty,
but I can come
and help you after that.
Oh, great. The removal men are
bringing the last load over
in about an hour.
I'll be as quick as I can.
And, please...
..don't ever say "sexy time"
in my presence again.
Can we do this tomorrow?
I've got a new cafe to open.
SHE CHUCKLES
HE SIGHS
That was embarrassing.
she said
The way we come to be
Yeah, it's a big old world indeed
And everyone conspires
Where all light comes in
Mrs Palmer?
Morning.  Morning.
If you could pop that...
How's it going?
Oh! Well, that depends.
If you like to be surrounded
by boxes and not know
where anything is whilst
being pecked to death
by a flock of seagulls,
it's going great.
Mm! I thought the Inspector
would be here helping.
He offered, but...
..things tend to take a little
longer when he helps,
so I said he'd be better at work.
Mm. I feel your pain.
I thought it was a college day.
I switched so I can help Martha
with the move.
You don't mind, do you?
She's a life-saver.
No, as long as she doesn't
fall behind with her work.
Is that why you're here?
Checking up on me?
No. I was hoping I'd get a coffee.
Well, that's not happening.
I don't even know where the coffee
machine is,
let alone where to plug it in,
never mind coffee beans or milk.
Not a problem.
I'll leave you to it.
And if you want a full day's
work out of madam here,
you might need to
take her phone off her.
You know, I read this thing
last week about a girl in the US
who divorced her parents.
I'll sue you for maintenance.
PHONE RINGS
Have fun.
Sergeant Williams.
Where?
Yeah. Yeah, that one.
OK. On my way.
Oh, erm, you know,
lots of reasons, really.
Erm, well, it's in the heart
of town, you know,
which is, erm...which
is...which is good.
And, erm, the landlord
of the last place
was a right pain in the backside.
SHE CHUCKLES
And I did offer to help with
the move, you know, but, erm,
Martha insisted that
I came to work instead.
Ah!
I'm sure she knows best.
I'll get maintenance
to take a look.
We've got maintenance?